But in her case, she's cute, funny, and the most powerful person in the world.
Dads have such busy schedules.
He'll send in a script two days in advance and say he's sorry, but...
He's like, "I'm sorry two days in advance, but I'll get it all in.
I only know people in Tokyo who do that.
I'm so jealous that you have a producer who can see things objectively.
I'd like to get started on the project again.
Let's have people in the industry remember this project!
It's already a regular project.
It's a good learning experience.
This time again, we're going to invite a director of a famous TV show.
I'm going to invite directors and writers of famous TV programs.
I thought, "Let's give them a chance to remember me and give them a boost.
And we succeeded.
Why do you want to give them a piece of the action?
Once, I got along with a professor at Yomiuri.
We succeeded.
Mr. Hiyoki from Fuji Television.
The result was good.
So we're hoping for the same thing this time.
Then, I'd like to invite you right away.
This way, please.
Please come in.
So, this time, we have a person from TV Asahi.
He's working for TV Asahi, planning programs such as Sakura Mitsu and Ano Channel.
Ms. Teruwa Koyama.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm sorry.
So, Teruha-san would be a Kajihan, right?
I see. That's why my boss is Kajihan.
I started out as an AD for Ametalk.
I've been doing it for about five years now.
I've been with the company since my first year.
He's my senior who's been taking care of me since I first joined the company.
But Mr. Kaji knew that there was a girl who was doing really well in comedy.
I think he might be talking about Saito-san.
Wow!
I've also been asked to let you know if there are any interesting kids out there.
I'd like to know if there are any interesting kids out there.
Saito is not only a great comedian, but he also has a number of pin stories.
All the plays are there.
I have a show lesson next week.
Mr. Sakuma will be judging the show lesson.
You're entering a show lesson I'm judging?
Yes, I am.
Uh-huh.
I'm a judge for the finals.
Don't be silly.
But I'm in the finals.
If I make it to the finals, Mr. Sakuma will be there.
A show lesson for radio personalities under 25
It's sponsored by Osaka Japan.
You're entering it?
Yes, I am.
You can do whatever you want.
The reason we asked Ms. Yama to come this time is...
He's probably the closest in age to idols in the TV industry.
He's a producer who loves idols.
I see.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, you've been working with underground idols for a while.
That's right.
Underground idols are more embarrassing than anything else.
I've been working with underground idols for a long time.
Underground idols...
What?
What? Huh? What?
I was a little bit of an underground idol.
But I've always really loved it.
I'm like a nerd.
I guess it just grew out of love.
A friend of mine asked me to join.
I just started out as a casual observer.
But you have a unique background.
After being an idol
You entered TV after having worked as an idol.
So, Koyama-san, do you have anything you want to say to the lovebirds?
Well, I had a lot of experience deep underground, so...
I hope you guys don't feel bad about it.
I hope you don't have any bad feelings about it.
I hope you don't feel bad about it, but you are in a very privileged environment.
I envy you.
Yes, I envy you.
I used to work with my uncle.
We should get together on Mixi or something.
Get together on Mixi?
I met him on Mixi.
You were doing it with someone you met on Mixi?
Yeah.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Oh, it's a new era.
That's amazing.
It's interesting.
So you're like that Sakuma guy.
Yes, that's right.
He's active in various media, not only on TV.You've been active in various media, not only on TV.
I am very jealous that there is a producer who can look at things objectively
I envy you so much.
I'm blessed to be in such a good environment.
You are the founder of that channel, aren't you, Mr. Hut?
That's right.
That channel is amazing, isn't it?
I think the gap between Ano's cute looks and her actions
The gap between Ano's cute appearance and her actions, or rather, the interestingness of her actions, coexist.
With comedians, being cute is a bit of a distraction.
The idol-like element is not necessary.
But in Ano's case, she has both.
She's cute and funny, the best of both worlds.
No matter who comes as a guest, Anochan is always the same.
It's interesting that no matter who comes to the show, she always has the same self.
It's amazing.
And Fujisaki loves Ano?
Master Ano... master Ano...
Ano-sama?
But he's new.
New?
That's an idol term.
I've only started liking you recently, but you still like me.
But I really like you and Iguchi-san.
That was so cute... that's why you like her so much.
I watched it on TV.
I love it.
That's nice.
I'm glad.
I see. That's why Sakura Mitzumo is a little different.
Sometimes they do things that the comedians come up with.
So are the four members of the show really great?
I think it's a burden for Plaza Pappa, who has a very busy schedule, to have to take on all the work for this project.
He has to put everything in his head. You do it all in a single shot for every recording.
We rehearse, but the actual performance is a one-shot. But they put it all in.
So we have never failed to get it right.
We would give him the script two days before the performance, saying we were sorry for the trouble we had caused, and he would then put in all the lines, even though there were quite a lot of them.
When do you think he sleeps?
Only Tokyo Zero Sun seems to know that.
Only Tokyo Zero Sun puts it in no matter when I give it to them.
What I think is amazing about professional idols is that Takeeda once told me he was going to do a manzai with Shiori Tamai of Gomukuro, and he arranged it right before the show.
We only had to do it once.
The script was originally submitted, but when they did it just once before the performance, it was perfect.
Perfect.
He said he would do better than perfect.
To be honest, he was better than me.
The tone of the lines and so on.
I thought, "Idols are amazing.
Idols have a different level of concentration.
They are so focused.
My daughter is also a fan of Sakurazaka and Keyaki, and she went to one of their live performances.
Yes.
I wondered if she had any fans, because she got a letter back from them, and she wrote back to Akimoto Yasushi saying that this part of your death was wonderful.
It was quite amazing.
You, a fan of Zelkova, were a fan of Death? He said.
Mr. Okuno.
I was a fan of Akimoto-san.
My eighth grade daughter.
It's wonderful that she can see Okuno.
In front of the embarrassed Keyaki people, she said she was a fan of our daughter.
But, like Ano-chan, like Sakurazaka, producers, you know, they fall in love with you and make you.
Well, it's the same with my comedians, but if you don't make someone want you to be more visible to the world, you won't find anyone who will support you.
I think that's a very beautiful word for a good thing.
But we were also numb to it just now. That's what I think.
A proposal is not born, right?
A proposal is never born, right? You can't write one without that one zero first thought.
That's right.
Now, we have heard a lot of things so far, but I would like to start with a project like this.
I know because I am a producer who works with idols. This is an important point!
Now, I would like to ask Ms. Koyama to answer some of the points that she would like to convey to the members in the preliminary meeting with the staff.
I'd like to cover them in the form of a quiz.
So, is this something that is really useful?
In front of idols, that is.
Let's do it.
You're trying to get into it, aren't you?
Suddenly, after hearing what you just said, you're trying to jump over the riffraff and get into it.
That's not the best thing to do. It's not like I'm going to guess once.
Now then, let's go. Here's the first point that might be important.
Send out a 00.
Let's have everyone in the riffraff raise their hands and answer the word that goes in this 00. It is 00.
Quiz style!
Transmitting the moon.
Correct answer!
Well, yes. He likes her too.
I can understand. What do you mean by "send out the moon"?
It can be anything you really like, but even if you think it's a silly thing like this, you should transmit it every day.
It is better to send out something every day, even if you think it might be a trivial thing. The reason for this is that the casting people have a profile, but they don't know if you really like something or not,
So, this is something that really happened to me,
I want to know if there are any girls who like gummy bears. That's the kind of research I would do. If I said that I was going to a gummy factory for a TV show, they would ask me if there were any gummy girls who liked gummy bears,
I think there are some people who have actually gotten business from her. There are also people who connect with her through her ramen messages and so on.
So, no matter how trivial it is, you should put it out there. If you put something in writing, send out a message, or send out a video or whatever, it will probably catch on in some way.
I think it is better not to have a business mindset of hoping that it will lead to something.
That is true.
Is anyone sending out anything? Right now. Fujisaki.
I've been recommending anime and posting the URLs of my favorite manga right away.
I've compiled a list of all the spring anime. I've put together a list of spring anime that I recommend.
It's good, isn't it?
Saito.
I'm on TikTok every day now.
I've been there for a day.I was there for a day.
I understand. It's the Japanese Grand Prix.
My first idol.
Mr. Sasaki.
I love gummy bears, and I put gummy bears on my website, and thankfully, I became an honorary member of the Japan Gummy Association.
Seriously? Honorary member?
Become an honorary member. Soon.
I don't have the strength to be an honorary member yet.
I'm not strong enough.
A little bit.
Yoshimura.
I like sweet drinks, so I'm working on a project where I make cocktails and post them on Instagram.
It's really cool.
I recently got certified as a cocktail meister, and I would like to introduce various kinds of cocktails.
That's great. Everyone is steadily trying various things.
It's important, isn't it? It is important, isn't it?
Are there any members who haven't done so yet who would like to do so?
Ah, Hayashi.
I would like to promote kendo.
That's right. You were doing it, right?
But kendo smells like a kotei.
And now...
That's enough.
It's like musu-musu.
It's annoying.
It's okay, it's okay.
Okay, now, here's the next important duck point.
XXX wins, not death.
Now, what is it that goes into this XX? Yes, Saito.
Running away wins, not dying.
Well, yeah. No, but that's not what I mean.
Now, ________ wins, you don't die. Yes, Hayashi.
Failure wins, not death.
Well, well, well, well, that's a good word.
It's a good word too, but a little more.
Yes, Nagamatsu.
Trying wins, not dying.
Yes, but in a nuanced way. It's getting closer as a nuance.
Yes, Fujii.
Dying is winning.
Wait! Wait!
Hayashi.
You jump in, you win, you don't die.
Well, well, well, well. It'll happen. It'll happen.
We're all close. Yes, Natsume.
Live to win, don't die.
He's the only one who's out of focus.
Everyone else is jumping in with a challenge or something.
Live to win, don't die.
That's right.
What do you guys want this recording to be? This recording.
Tell me how you want this recording.
Yes, Saito.
It's hard, but it's a win-win. You're not going to die.
What? The pain?
It's hard to enjoy.
I don't have a heart.
I'm having fun.
Oh, what? Why?
What is it?
Yes, Natsume.
Enjoyment wins, not death.
You're right.
You just took it away from me.
It means enjoyment wins, not death.
What does this mean?
I'm especially good on location,
One of everyone,
When one of us is going to be on location with Mr. Horiken,
I get really nervous.
I feel like I'm outside the studio,
It was like no one else was there.
But today was the day,
I always tell them to have fun,
I always tell them to have fun.
I always tell them to enjoy themselves as if it were a field trip.
I don't know,
I always tell them to enjoy themselves as if it were a field trip,
They think everything is a job, and they feel like they have to get results,
I always say, "Have fun,
But in the first place, it's my life,
I think everything is a good experience,
Enjoy it,
You have nothing to lose,
I have nothing to lose, so I don't care how much I slip,
I'm not going to die,
If I slip, people will laugh at me,
If I make someone laugh, it's like a family,
If you can make someone laugh, you have nothing to lose,
I think it's good to enjoy that much too,
That's what I think of in all my work.
This is true, isn't it?
It is better to have fun,
It's a bit difficult in some ways.
I know that,
I know that, but there are some members who are troubled when they slip up,
It's the same for me.
It's the whole world.
The whole world is watching.
The whole world is watching.In the World Roundup.
Takeshi's stuff is good.
He was depressed, right?
He was depressed with Takeshi-san,
He said, "The young people today don't need us to tell them what to do.
We should teach them everything,
He said, "They probably don't understand anything anymore,
I was the first one to be told that they probably don't know what they're doing anymore,
I was thinking about it for another hour.
I don't know what to do, Takeshi.
But that too,
But now that I think about it, there were people who laughed at me,
I guess I should have just enjoyed it.
I thought, "Wow, I slipped today.
I thought I was slipping today.
When I entered the "Dawn" part of the comedy,
I thought about it and thought about it,
You don't enjoy it?
No, I don't enjoy it.
When it comes to comedy,
I'm always thinking about the reactions of the staff and their faces.
How do you feel about that?
From the perspective of the creator,
The people who are doing it are listening to that.
No, but even if you slip,
But if you slip, you can do something if you play something.
If you don't ask about trans, you can't compete,
I think, "Oh, oh," so I'm a staff member.
I don't know what to do.
Because on a day-to-day basis, it's me who reflects,
You have to admit that you are the type of person who reflects on yourself,
I have to make up my mind that I'm the type of person who reflects,
You should write a reflection poem every day.
Good advice.
Poems of reflection.
Write a reflection poem.
Eat it,
When you have enough for about three months, bring it to me.
Okita.
You can be 21 works.
21 works, Sakuma-san.
I'll try.
Then, let's come to the next important point.
This way.
A person who can fight with ________ can fight anywhere.
Now, what will be in this XX?
Yes, Natsume.
People who can fight in O-Kiri can fight anywhere.
Because he is a comedian.
Yes, Hayashi.
Those who can fight with Sakuma's backing can fight anywhere.
Hey, that's not a good idea.
Don't let young people use the word "stand behind.
Big guys say it too much.
Yes, Hizusaki.
People who can fight naked can fight anywhere.
Why do you say I can fight naked?
Feelings? Naked feelings.
I see. But that's not what I mean.
It's something more concrete.
Yes, Nagamatsu.
People who can fight in the world can fight anywhere.
It was a matter of course.
Yes, Saito.
People who can fight at home can fight anywhere.
You mean you can fight at home?
If you are strong at home, you can do your best in a situation like this.
What do you mean by that? When it comes to Jackie,
You mean you can fight at home with the weapons you have at home?
That's not what I'm saying.
Yes, Himinos.
A man who can fight on location can fight anywhere.
Well, it's different, but close. That's the framework.
Location and variety collectively, yes, Nagamatsu.
Those who can fight on TV can fight anywhere.
That is correct.
What does this mean?
The TV scene is the most difficult, because it is a living organism,
There is a script, but it changes completely depending on the situation.
You never know where the right answer is. You never know.
The fact that we are trying to get results there is the challenge,
I think you are challenging yourself to do something that is a very high hurdle to begin with.
So, if I can compete on TV, then I will be able to compete on radio,
If you can compete on TV, you can do radio, live performances, talk shows, and so on,
I feel that the ultimate goal is to become a major artist from the very beginning.
I feel that the final goal was set as a major goal from the very beginning,
But I don't think that's wrong at all.
Which part do you look for first?
The rough stones, like that. And then, if the girl is an idol or something.
What kind of atmosphere do you get from the girl?
I think that videos are the best way to get a feel for what the girl is like in real life.
So, if I am interested in a girl, I watch her videos on YouTube.
I see.
My question is, when you do research,
Which YouTube site do you watch first?
You're the one I'm trying to get into the most.
I was wondering what you watch.
Is it Twitter, Instagram, or YouTube that this person is interested in?
For comedians, of course I look at Twitter,
And I also look at YouTube,
If he/she is on the radio, I listen to the radio and so on.If you are on the radio, do you listen to the radio or something?
That way.
You mean Saito's "big comedy" is also good, right? The video is good, too.
But it doesn't get any views at all.
But even that is interesting.
It's not a big hit at all,
There is an idol who just does comedy every day.
That's interesting, and I think it's good.
That's great.
Well, I'm going to end with this,
Please just watch it.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Please do so.
I want to do something on your show!
I want to be on your show!
You want to be on Kaj's show?
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry if there is some kind of ritual here.
I think I'm going to raise my hand.
I want to be on the show.
Yui Takahashi's Hot and Spicy Expedition!
Yay!
Thank you!
Delicious!
Don't let them in!
Oh, shit.
Around here?
I have to be aware of where I am when Takanashi is the main attraction.
If this is really a normal VD and I'm directing...
I might not need to use so much of Natsume's sound.
I might be like...
Just a little bit and you'll think it's all right.
That's a tension mistake.
Then let's watch the rest of the show.
I'm afraid to watch the rest of the show.
Thank you for watching today.
You're subscribed, right?
Oh, thank God.
You did, didn't you?
You did, too.
Did you?
Did you know?
Yes!
Yeah, of course you knew.
What's that? You knew?
I knew it!
Wait a minute.
You,
You forgot the blood!
So, subscribe to our channel.
Please subscribe to our channel!